Class of 1962 Records, 1958-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1962 Records
1958-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1962.
RG 80
3 boxes (2.1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1962.
Historical Note
The Class of 1962 was the eighty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1962 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1962, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1962 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Photographs 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 2)
- Freshman Handbook 1958 (Box 2226, Folder 3)
- General 1960-1962 (Box 2226, Folder 4)
- Groups 1958-1959 (Box 2226, Folder 5)
- History 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1966-1976 (Box 2226, Folder 9)
- Class Letters 1997-2001 (Box 2226, Folder 10)
- Officers 1959 (Box 2226, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2226, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 2226, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1977 (Box 2226, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1982 (Box 2226, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 2226, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2226, Folder 17)
- Who's Who 1958 (Box 2226, Folder 18)